artuji.com 2016-11-27

# Privacy Policy - Artuji

Your privacy is respected here in my site, [www.artuji.com](http://www.artuji.com/ "Artuji"). Please read below the disclosures regarding information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site.

**Log Files**  
My web site server generates log files. The information being saved are internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, internet service providers, visitor entry and exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and visitor clicks. These data are used to analyze trends, administer the site, track the browsing behavior of the visitors, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**E-mail Subscription**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to my posts via e-mail (powered by Feedburner), I ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for my users’ privacy, a way to opt-out of these communications is provided.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. My site use cookies for tracking visitors’ activity. Some of my business partners and advertisers use cookies on our site. However, I have no access to or control over these cookies, once I have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. You can choose not to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. At any time, you may remove any cookie stored on your hard drive by deleting them in your browser’s settings section.

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. I encourage my users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Advertisers**  
I use outside ad companies to display ads on my site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and I do not have access to these information. I work with the ad companies like Google Adsense. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

**Google and the[DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx)**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Affiliates**  
I am also an affiliate for Paypal and many other affiliate marketing companies. I do not have control over their privacy practices so I would advise that before you sign up for an account in these companies, please check their websites for their respective privacy statements.

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding my privacy policy, please contact me by filling up the [contact form](http://www.artuji.com/contact "Contact The Artuji Admin").
